{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":24723,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":62,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Image_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_21","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_2","title":"Oscar Mendez Module #2  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_2","title":"Reading a Nutritional Facts Label ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11954","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11967","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_23","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12004","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_21","Button_1","si11954","si11967","Image_23"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":798},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12004"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_93","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_93","title":"From memory, middle-school wrestlers will be able to Explain why one should consider reading a nutrition facts label giving two reasons. Using a nutrition label and Nutrition Label Checklist, middle-school wrestlers will be able to:  Apply the 5 and 20 rule to describe the percent daily value of Total Fat with 100% accuracy. Apply the 5 and 20 rule to describe Saturated Fat with 100% accuracy Explain whether this food should be avoided based on trans fat with 100% accuracy. Apply the 5 and 20 rule to describe the percent daily value of Total Carbohydrate with 100% accuracy. Apply the 5 and 20 rule to describe the percent daily value of Dietary Fiber with 100% accuracy. Apply the 5 and 20 rule to describe the percent daily value of Added Sugar with 100% accuracy.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_42","title":"Learning Objectives ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_81","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41436","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41449","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_82","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41481","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41494","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_96","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_96","title":"Describe why grams of Protein are used over percent daily value with 100% accuracy. Track their grams of Total Fat with 100% accuracy. Track their grams of Total Carbohydrates with 100% accuracy Track their grams of Protein with 100% accuracy. Using the Macronutrients and Calorie Tracking Journal, middle-school wrestlers will be able to  calculate the total amount of calories in a meal with 100% accuracy. calculate the total amount of fat in a meal with 100% accuracy. calculate the total amount of carbohydrates in a meal with 100% accuracy. calculate the total amount of calories in a meal with 100% accuracy. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide41512","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_93","Button_81","si41436","si41449","Button_82","si41481","si41494","Text_Caption_96"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":399},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide41512"}}},{"id":"si44108","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44115","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"1. What are the two reasons why one should consider reading a nutrition label? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44130","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44134","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Help you track your nutritional intake ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44134","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide44078q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si44130_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Help you track your nutritional intake\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":5}}}},{"id":"si44141","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44145","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Provides information for a serving ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44145","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide44078q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si44141_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Provides information for a serving\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":5}}}},{"id":"si44372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44376","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Improve your wrestling stamina ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44376","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide44078q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si44372_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Improve your wrestling stamina\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si44387","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44391","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Includes tips on avoiding unhealthy food ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44391","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide44078q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si44387_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Includes tips on avoiding unhealthy food\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si44402","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44406","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Offers peronalized meal plans ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44406","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide44078q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si44402_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Offers peronalized meal plans\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si44162","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si44166","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide44078q0","for":"Slide44078q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44183","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide44078q0","for":"Slide44078q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44196","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide44078q0","for":"Slide44078q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44149","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide44078q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide44078","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si44108","si44115","si44134","si44145","si44376","si44391","si44406","si44166","si44183","si44196","si44149"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":111},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide44078"},"question":{"interactionId":"44095","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1. What are the two reasons why one should consider reading a nutrition label?\r","ikc":false,"type":"pretest","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A","B"]}}},{"id":"si44865","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_175","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44877","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_176","title":"2. What is the “5 and 20” Rule? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44888","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_177","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44892","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_178","title":"A rule that recommends 20 servings of of fruits and vegetables to consume 5 days a week ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44888_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A rule that recommends 20 servings of of fruits and vegetables to consume 5 days a week\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si44899","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_179","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44903","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_180","title":"A guideline that considers 5% or less of a nutrient to be low and 20% or more to be high. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44899_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A guideline that considers 5% or less of a nutrient to be low and 20% or more to be high.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si44910","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_181","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44914","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_182","title":"A rule that suggests to drink five glasses of water a day and drinkink 20 ounces of soda a week. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44910_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A rule that suggests to drink five glasses of water a day and drinkink 20 ounces of soda a week.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si44921","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_183","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44925","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_184","title":"A standard procedure of warming up for 5 minutes and resistance training of 20 minutes.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44921_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A standard procedure of warming up for 5 minutes and resistance training of 20 minutes. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si44980","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","roles":{}},{"id":"si45010","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_52","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45048q1","for":"Slide45048q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45022","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45048q1","for":"Slide45048q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45048q1","for":"Slide45048q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44974","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_37","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide45048q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide45048","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si44865","si44877","si44892","si44903","si44914","si44925","si45010","si45022","si45034","si44974"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide45048"},"question":{"interactionId":"44850","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. What is the “5 and 20” Rule?\r","ikc":false,"type":"pretest","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"Image_89","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_89","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide45064q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45111","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Matching ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45118","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3. Using the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45125","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45149","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45153","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45170","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Saturated Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45136","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45159","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45163","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Low source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45163ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si45180","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Medium source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45184ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si45201","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45205","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"High source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45205ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si45223","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si45227","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45064q2","for":"Slide45064q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45244","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45064q2","for":"Slide45064q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45257","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45064q2","for":"Slide45064q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51724","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide45064q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide45064","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_89","si45111","si45118","si45163","si45184","si45205","si45227","si45244","si45257","si51724"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":177},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide45064"},"question":{"interactionId":"45081","quizId":389,"title":"Matching","text":"3. Using the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients:\r","type":"pretest","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"Image_96","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_96","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide45527q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45564","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"4. Based on trans fat, this food should be avoided. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45579","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45583","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True; This food should be avoided based on trans fat. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45579_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True; This food should be avoided based on trans fat.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si45590","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45594","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False; This food does not need to be avoided based on trans fat. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45590_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False; This food does not need to be avoided based on trans fat.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si45611","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si45615","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45527q3","for":"Slide45527q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45632","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45527q3","for":"Slide45527q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45645","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45527q3","for":"Slide45527q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide45527q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide45527","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_96","si45557","si45564","si45583","si45594","si45615","si45632","si45645","si45598"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":108},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide45527"},"question":{"interactionId":"45544","quizId":389,"title":"True/False","text":"4. Based on trans fat, this food should be avoided.\r","ikc":false,"type":"pretest","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Image_90","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_90","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide45508q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45302","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","roles":{}},{"id":"si45314","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_187","title":"Matching ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45326","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_188","title":"5. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45333","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_58","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_59","title":"Total Carbohydrate ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_95","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_95","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","title":"Dietary Fiber ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45518","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45522","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Added Sugar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45370","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_115","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45374","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_189","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45378","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_190","title":"Low source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45378ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si45384","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_191","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45388","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_192","title":"Medium source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45388ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si45394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_193","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_194","title":"High source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45398ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si45470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_57","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45508q4","for":"Slide45508q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45482","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45508q4","for":"Slide45508q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45494","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45508q4","for":"Slide45508q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45440","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_67","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide45508q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide45508","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_90","si45314","si45326","si45378","si45388","si45398","si45470","si45482","si45494","si45440"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":177},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide45508"},"question":{"interactionId":"45278","quizId":389,"title":"Matching","text":"5. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients:\r","type":"pretest","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"Image_91","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_91","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide45914q5"},"question":{"quizId":389,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_116","roles":{}},{"id":"si45709","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_195","title":"Matching ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45721","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_196","title":"6. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_117","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_118","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_118","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_197","title":"Vitamin D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_198","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_199","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_199","title":"Calcium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_200","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_200","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_201","title":"Iron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Potassium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45775","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_202","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45779","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_203","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45783","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_204","title":"Low source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45783ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si45789","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_205","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45793","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_206","title":"Medium source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45793ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si45799","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_207","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_208","title":"High source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45803ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si45875","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_58","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45914q5","for":"Slide45914q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45887","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45914q5","for":"Slide45914q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45899","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide45914q5","for":"Slide45914q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si45845","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_68","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide45914q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide45914","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_91","si45709","si45721","si45783","si45793","si45803","si45875","si45887","si45899","si45845"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":177},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide45914"},"question":{"interactionId":"45666","quizId":389,"title":"Matching","text":"6. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients:\r","type":"pretest","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"Image_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_92","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46250","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_211","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46262","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_212","title":"7. Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per serving, which of the following would be considered medium in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46273","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_227","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_228","title":"Total Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"85","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46273_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"86","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46284","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_229","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46288","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_230","title":"Saturated Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46288","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"87","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46284_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"88","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saturated Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46295","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_231","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46299","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_232","title":"Cholesterol ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46299","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"89","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46295_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"90","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cholesterol\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46306","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_233","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46310","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_234","title":"Sodium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46310","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"91","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46306_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"92","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sodium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46317","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_235","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46321","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_236","title":"Total Carbs. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46321","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"93","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46317_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"94","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Carbs.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46441","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Dietary Fibers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46445","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46441_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Dietary Fibers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46456","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46460","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Added Sugar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46460","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46456_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Added Sugar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46471","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"H) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46475","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vitamin D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46475","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46471_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vitamin D\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46486","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46490","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Calcium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46490","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46486_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Calcium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"J) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46505","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Iron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46505","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si46501_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Iron\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52369","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"K) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52373","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Potassium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52373","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52369_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Potassium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si46365","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_210","roles":{}},{"id":"si46395","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_60","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide46433q6","for":"Slide46433q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46407","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide46433q6","for":"Slide46433q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46419","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide46433q6","for":"Slide46433q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46359","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_70","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46433q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide46433","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_92","si46250","si46262","si46277","si46288","si46299","si46310","si46321","si46445","si46460","si46475","si46490","si46505","si52373","si46395","si46407","si46419","si46359"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":222},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide46433"},"question":{"interactionId":"46235","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7. Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per serving, which of the following would be considered medium in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply\r","ikc":false,"type":"pretest","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A","B","E","F","G","J"]}}},{"id":"Image_94","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_94","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"question":{"quizId":389,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52454","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_366","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_367","title":"8. Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per cookie, which of the following would be considered high in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_368","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_369","title":"Total Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"85_178","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52477_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"86_179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52488","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_370","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52492","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_371","title":"Saturated Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52492","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"87_179","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52488_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"88_180","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saturated Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52499","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_372","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52503","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_373","title":"Cholesterol ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52503","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"89_180","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52499_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"90_181","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cholesterol\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52510","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_374","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52514","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_375","title":"Sodium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52514","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"91_181","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52510_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"92_182","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sodium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52521","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_376","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52525","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_377","title":"Total Carbs. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52525","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"93_182","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52521_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"94_183","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Carbs.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52532","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_378","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_379","title":"Dietary Fibers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"183","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52532_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"184","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Dietary Fibers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52543","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_380","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52547","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_381","title":"Added Sugar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52547","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"185","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52543_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"186","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Added Sugar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52554","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_382","title":"H) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52558","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_383","title":"Vitamin D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52558","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"187","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52554_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"188","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vitamin D\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52565","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_384","title":"I) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52569","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_385","title":"Calcium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52569","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"189","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52565_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"190","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Calcium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52576","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_386","title":"J) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52580","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_387","title":"Iron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52580","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"191","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52576_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"192","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Iron\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52587","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_388","title":"K) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52591","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_389","title":"Potassium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52591","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"193","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si52587_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"194","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Potassium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si52635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_390","roles":{}},{"id":"si52665","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_96","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide52703q7","for":"Slide52703q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide52703q7","for":"Slide52703q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52689","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide52703q7","for":"Slide52703q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si52629","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_90","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide52703q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide52703","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_94","si52454","si52466","si52481","si52492","si52503","si52514","si52525","si52536","si52547","si52558","si52569","si52580","si52591","si52665","si52677","si52689","si52629"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":195},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide52703"},"question":{"interactionId":"52427","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per cookie, which of the following would be considered high in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply\r","ikc":false,"type":"pretest","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B","E","F","G","J"]}}},{"id":"Image_97","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_97","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46809q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46831","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Fill-In-The-Blank ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46838","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"9. Complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46850","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"There are dash grams of total fat, dash grams of total carbohydrates, and dash grams of protein in this label. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46850_q1_answer_0_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si46850_q1_answer_1_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si46850_q1_answer_2_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si46867","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si46871","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide46809q8","for":"Slide46809q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46888","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide46809q8","for":"Slide46809q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46901","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide46809q8","for":"Slide46809q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46854","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide46809q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide46809","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_97","si46831","si46838","si46871","si46888","si46901","si46854"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide46809"},"question":{"interactionId":"46825","quizId":389,"title":"Fill-In-The-Blank","text":"9. Complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks.\r","type":"pretest","ikc":false,"interactionType":"fill-in","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"Image_98","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_98","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_99","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_99","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_100","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_92","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_93","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_93","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_94","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_94","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si46980","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_216","roles":{}},{"id":"si46992","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_217","title":"Fill-In-The-Blank ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_218","title":"10. Use the three labels to calculate the total amount per macronutrient. Complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47014","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_209","title":"After calculating the total for all three labels, “Total fat” is at dash, “Total Carbohydrates” is at dash , and “Protein” is at dash. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47014_q1_answer_0_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47014_q1_answer_1_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47014_q1_answer_2_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47080","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_85","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47118q9","for":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47092","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47118q9","for":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47104","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47118q9","for":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47050","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_72","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47118q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide47118","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_98","Image_99","Image_100","SmartShape_92","SmartShape_93","SmartShape_94","si46992","si47004","si47080","si47092","si47104","si47050"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":186},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide47118"},"question":{"interactionId":"46952","quizId":389,"title":"Fill-In-The-Blank","text":"10. Use the three labels to calculate the total amount per macronutrient. Complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks.\r","type":"pretest","ikc":false,"interactionType":"fill-in","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_6","title":"Consulting A Doctor ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"Before making any changes to your diet or weight, consult with a professional within their own scope of practice: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"Doctor ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"Registered Dietitian or Nutritionist ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16483","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16496","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16528","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16541","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"The focus of this will be to provide general advice on how to read a nutritional facts panel and how to track your calories and macronutrients. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide3_Consultation_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Slide3_Consultation_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16578","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_14","Text_Caption_15","Text_Caption_16","Button_4","si16483","si16496","Button_5","si16528","si16541","Text_Caption_17","Slide3_Consultation_5"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":513},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16578"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_7","title":"Nutritional Facts Label  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"Located in the back or side of the food package servings per container and serving size Total calories Macronutrients Cholesterol, sodium and dietary fibers Vitamins and nutrients ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16686","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16699","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16731","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16744","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_22","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_22","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_25","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_92","title":"Link to Checklist (Google Doc) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_66","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16781","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_19","Button_6","si16686","si16699","Button_7","si16731","si16744","Image_22","SmartShape_20","SmartShape_21","SmartShape_22","SmartShape_23","SmartShape_24","SmartShape_25","SmartShape_26","Text_Caption_92","SmartShape_66"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":582},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16781"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_36","title":"Reasons to Read a Nutritional Facts Label  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":"Help you track your nutritional intake Use grams listed for macronutrients Check for “empty calories” Provides information for a serving Serving size: amount expected to eat in one sitting Important: Percent daily value (%DV) is based on a 2,000-calorie diet Calorie needs can vary ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_46","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_67","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si36091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si36104","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_68","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si36136","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si36149","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_45","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide36193","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_84","Image_46","Button_67","si36091","si36104","Button_68","si36136","si36149","Image_45","SmartShape_28"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":708},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide36193"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_8","title":"5 and 20 Rule for Percent Daily Value (%DV) ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"If Percentage Daily Value (%DV) is: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"5% or less = Low in that specific nutrient ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16895","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16908","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16940","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si16953","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_85","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_85","title":"Moderate/Medium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"20% or more = High in that specific nutrient. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"0 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","title":"2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":"5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"20 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_2","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_3","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_4","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_5","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_6","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_7","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_8","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_9","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_10","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","title":"6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_71","title":"7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_11","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_12","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_13","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_14","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_16","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_17","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_18","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_19","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_72","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_72","title":"3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_73","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":"4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_74","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_74","title":"8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":"9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","title":"16 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_77","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_77","title":"17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":"18 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_79","title":"19 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","title":"21 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_81","title":"22 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"23 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_7","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_20","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_21","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide16973","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_22","Text_Caption_23","Button_8","si16895","si16908","Button_9","si16940","si16953","Text_Caption_85","Text_Caption_24","Text_Caption_65","SmartShape_4","Text_Caption_66","Text_Caption_67","Text_Caption_68","Text_Caption_69","Text_Caption_70","Text_Caption_71","Text_Caption_72","Text_Caption_73","Text_Caption_74","Text_Caption_75","Text_Caption_76","Text_Caption_77","Text_Caption_78","Text_Caption_79","Text_Caption_80","Text_Caption_81","Text_Caption_82","SmartShape_7","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_83","SmartShape_5","SmartShape_11","SmartShape_12","SmartShape_13"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":579},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16973"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_23","title":"“Per Serving”  and “Per Container” ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","title":"Newer labels with servings of 3 or less will include calories of the entire package Important for those who eat a bag in one sitting % DV increases in specific macronutrients, but still has limited micronutrients. Empty calories: High in calories with no nutritional value ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_37","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19517","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19530","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_38","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19562","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19575","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_25","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_26","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19595","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_51","Button_37","si19517","si19530","Button_38","si19562","si19575","Image_25","Image_26","SmartShape_27","SmartShape_29"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":849},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19595"}}},{"id":"Image_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_47","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36224","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per package, which of the following would be considered medium in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36250","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si36246_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si36257","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36261","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Saturated Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36261","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si36257_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saturated Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si36517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Cholesterol ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36521","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si36517_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si36532","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36536","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Sodium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36536","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si36532_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sodium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si36547","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36551","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Carb. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36551","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si36547_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Carb.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si36562","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36566","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Dietary Fibers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36566","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si36562_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Dietary Fibers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37147","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37151","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vitamin D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37151","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37147_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vitamin D\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"H) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37166","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Calcium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37166","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37162_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Calcium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37177","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37181","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Iron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37181","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37177_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Iron\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37192","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"J) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37196","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Potassium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37196","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37192_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Potassium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si36278","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36194q10","for":"Slide36194q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36295","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36194q10","for":"Slide36194q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36194q10","for":"Slide36194q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37127","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si41890","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again; Medium source is between 5.1-19.9% ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36194q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide36194","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_47","si36224","si36231","si36250","si36261","si36521","si36536","si36551","si36566","si37151","si37166","si37181","si37196","si36278","si36295","si36308","si37127","si41890"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":321},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide36194"},"question":{"interactionId":"36211","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per package, which of the following would be considered medium in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","F","I"]}}},{"id":"Image_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_50","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_119","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37284","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_120","title":"Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per package, which of the following would be considered high in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37295","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_121","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37299","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_122","title":"Total Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37299","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"47","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37295_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"48","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37306","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_123","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37310","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_124","title":"Saturated Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37310","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"49","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37306_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"50","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saturated Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37317","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_125","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37321","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_126","title":"Cholesterol ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37321","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"51","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37317_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"52","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cholesterol\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37328","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_127","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37332","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_128","title":"Sodium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37332","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"53","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37328_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"54","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sodium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_129","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37343","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_130","title":"Total Carb. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37343","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"55","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37339_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"56","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Carb.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37350","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_131","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37354","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_132","title":"Dietary Fibers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37354","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"57","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37350_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"58","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Dietary Fibers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37361","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_133","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37365","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_134","title":"Vitamin D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37365","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"59","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37361_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"60","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vitamin D\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37372","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_135","title":"H) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37376","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_136","title":"Calcium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37376","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37372_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"62","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Calcium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37383","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_137","title":"I) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_138","title":"Iron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"63","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37383_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Iron\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_139","title":"J) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_140","title":"Potassium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"65","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si37394_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Potassium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_44","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37504q11","for":"Slide37504q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37447","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37504q11","for":"Slide37504q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37459","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37504q11","for":"Slide37504q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37490","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si42434","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again; High source is 20% or higher ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37504q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide37504","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_50","si37272","si37284","si37299","si37310","si37321","si37332","si37343","si37354","si37365","si37376","si37387","si37398","si37435","si37447","si37459","si37490","si42434"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":321},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide37504"},"question":{"interactionId":"37246","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per package, which of the following would be considered high in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply.\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D","E","H"]}}},{"id":"Image_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_24","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_10","title":"Locating Macronutrients ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"quiz","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"quiz","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17344","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17357","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si39475","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41999","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17389","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17402","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"fat","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"fat","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33451","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33465","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33786","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41985","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"cholandsodi","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"cholandsodi","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33543","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33570","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33800","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41943","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"carbohydrate","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"carbohydrate","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33636","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33663","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33772","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41971","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"protein","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"protein","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33729","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33756","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33758","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41957","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"vitamins","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"vitamins","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si39555","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si39582","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si39617","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si42014","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_80","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41292","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41306","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide17427","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"branching","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_24","quiz","si17344","si17357","si39475","si41999","Button_14","si17389","si17402","fat","si33451","si33465","si33786","si41985","cholandsodi","si33543","si33570","si33800","si41943","carbohydrate","si33636","si33663","si33772","si41971","protein","si33729","si33756","si33758","si41957","vitamins","si39555","si39582","si39617","si42014","Button_80","si41292","si41306"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":381},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17427"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_14","title":"Fat: What Numbers To Look At ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_27","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_28","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"1. Total Fat:  Use grams to track macronutrients. Use % to see if it is a low, medium, or high source. 2. Saturated fat: Use % to see if it is a low, medium, or high source. 3. Trans fat: Use % or grams to determine if we need to completely avoid it ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_21","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18163","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18176","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18208","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18221","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_98","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","title":"11 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_99","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_99","title":"Don’t need to avoid based on Trans Fat.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18241","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_27","Image_28","Text_Caption_37","Button_21","si18163","si18176","Button_22","si18208","si18221","SmartShape_30","SmartShape_31","SmartShape_32","Text_Caption_98","SmartShape_33","SmartShape_34","Text_Caption_99"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":750},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18241"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_15","title":"Fat in Almonds ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"1. Total Fat:  How many grams of fat? Is this source low, medium, or high in fat? 2. Saturated fat: Is this source low, medium, or high in saturated fat? 3. Trans fat: Should we avoid it based on trans fat? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_23","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18300","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18313","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_24","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18345","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18358","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_29","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"21 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_30","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"Don’t need to avoid based on Trans Fat.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_43","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18378","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_38","Button_23","si18300","si18313","Button_24","si18345","si18358","Image_29","Text_Caption_100","Image_30","Text_Caption_101","SmartShape_35","SmartShape_36","SmartShape_43"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1005},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18378"}}},{"id":"Image_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_31","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_32","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_16","title":"Fat: Knowledge Check ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"1. Total Fat:  How many grams of total fat? Is this source low, medium, or high in total fat? 2. Saturated fat: Is this source low, medium, or high in saturated fat? 3. Trans fat: Should we completely avoid it based on trans fat? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_25","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18437","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18450","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_26","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18482","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18495","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide18515","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_31","Image_32","Text_Caption_39","Button_25","si18437","si18450","Button_26","si18482","si18495"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":624},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18515"}}},{"id":"Image_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_35","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34271q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34301","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Fat: How many grams of total fat? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34327","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"15 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"15 grams\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"2 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34334_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"2 grams\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37512","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37516","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"10 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37512_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"10 grams\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37527","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37531","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"1.5 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37527_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1.5 grams\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37542","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37546","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Less than one gram ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37542_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Less than one gram\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34355","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34271q12","for":"Slide34271q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34271q12","for":"Slide34271q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34385","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34271q12","for":"Slide34271q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34342","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34271q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51893","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again! Remember to look at grams and not at % Daily Value. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34271q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34271","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_35","si34301","si34308","si34327","si34338","si37516","si37531","si37546","si34355","si34372","si34385","si34342","si51893"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":99},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34271"},"question":{"interactionId":"34288","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Total Fat: How many grams of total fat?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"]}}},{"id":"Image_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_78","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35151q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35007","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35019","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"Is this source low, medium, or high in total fat? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35030","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"Low ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35030_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si35041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35045","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"Medium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35041_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37561","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"High ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37557_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si35113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide35151q13","for":"Slide35151q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35125","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide35151q13","for":"Slide35151q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35137","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide35151q13","for":"Slide35151q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35083","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35151q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51906","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again - Remember the 5 and 20 rule. 0-5% Low; 5.1-19.9% Medium,  20%+ High. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35151q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide35151","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_78","si35007","si35019","si35034","si35045","si37561","si35113","si35125","si35137","si35083","si51906"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":132},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide35151"},"question":{"interactionId":"34981","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Is this source low, medium, or high in total fat?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"Image_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_79","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35337q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35205","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"Is this source low, medium or high in saturated fat? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35216","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"Low ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35216_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"7","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si35227","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35231","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"Medium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35227_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"9","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37572","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37576","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"High ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37572_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si35299","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide35337q14","for":"Slide35337q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35311","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide35337q14","for":"Slide35337q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide35337q14","for":"Slide35337q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35269","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35337q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again- Remember the 5 and 20 rule. 0-5% Low; 5.1-19.9% Medium,  20%+ High. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35337q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide35337","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_79","si35193","si35205","si35220","si35231","si37576","si35299","si35311","si35323","si35269","si51880"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":111},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide35337"},"question":{"interactionId":"35167","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Is this source low, medium or high in saturated fat?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"Image_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_80","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37779q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_141","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37636","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_142","title":"Should we avoid this food based on trans fat? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37647","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_143","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37651","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_144","title":"Yes, we should avoid this food based on trans fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37647_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"7_20","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, we should avoid this food based on trans fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37658","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_145","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37662","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_146","title":"No, we do not have to avoid this food based on trans fat. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37658_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"9_21","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, we do not have to avoid this food based on trans fat.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37741","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_45","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37779q15","for":"Slide37779q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37753","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37779q15","for":"Slide37779q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37765","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37779q15","for":"Slide37779q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37711","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37779q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51919","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Hint: Any amount of Trans fat should be avoided. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37779q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide37779","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_80","si37624","si37636","si37651","si37662","si37741","si37753","si37765","si37711","si51919"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":102},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide37779"},"question":{"interactionId":"37598","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Should we avoid this food based on trans fat?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"Image_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_33","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":389,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_35","title":"Hot Cheetos Summarization (Fat Section) ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"There are 10 grams of total fat.  This food is a medium source of total fat, as it provides 13% of daily value. This food is a medium source of saturated fat, as it provides 7% of daily value. We don’t have to avoid this food based on trans fat. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_65","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si34856","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si34869","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_66","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si34901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si34914","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_34","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_38","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34946","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_33","Text_Caption_64","Button_65","si34856","si34869","Button_66","si34901","si34914","Image_34","SmartShape_38"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1056},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34946"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_17","title":"Protein: Greek Yogurt ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"Percent daily value will  numbers vary. In example, 18 grams at 35% DV = ~50 grams of protein daily. 1. Protein Use grams to track macronutrients ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_27","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18628","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18641","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_28","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18673","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18686","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_40","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_41","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_44","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_40","Button_27","si18628","si18641","Button_28","si18673","si18686","Image_40","Image_41","SmartShape_44"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":645},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18706"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_18","title":"Protein: Protein Pancakes in Grams ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"1. Protein: How many grams of protein?    ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_29","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18765","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18778","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_30","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18810","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18823","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_42","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_44","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_86","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_86","title":"%DV should not be counted Greek yogurt: ~51 grams of daily protein intake Pancakes: ~88 grams of daily protein intake 15 grams at 17% DV    ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","title":"15 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_45","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18843","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_41","Button_29","si18765","si18778","Button_30","si18810","si18823","Image_42","Image_44","Text_Caption_86","Text_Caption_104","SmartShape_45"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":867},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18843"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_12","title":"Carbohydrate ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"1. Total Carbohydrate  Use grams to track macronutrients. Use % to see if it is a low, medium, or high source. 2. Dietary Fiber Use % to see if it is a low, medium, or high source. Soluble and insoluble will not be mentioned ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_17","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17781","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17794","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_18","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17826","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17839","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_57","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_57","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_56","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_39","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_40","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","title":"37 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_46","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17859","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_35","Button_17","si17781","si17794","Button_18","si17826","si17839","Image_57","Image_56","SmartShape_39","SmartShape_40","Text_Caption_105","SmartShape_46"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1038},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17859"}}},{"id":"Image_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_54","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_55","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_37","title":"Carbohydrate: Natural and Added Sugar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_87","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_87","title":"Total Sugar Includes Natural Sugar and Added Sugar 3. Added Sugar: Use % or grams to determine if there is any sugar added and if its less than 50 grams USDA recommends limiting to no more than 10% of total calories (50 grams of sugar) Sugar makes the food tastier and easier to overeat. Can easily add calories to your food. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_69","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si37913","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si37926","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_70","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si37958","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si37971","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"0 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_47","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_48","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide38015","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_54","Image_55","Text_Caption_87","Button_69","si37913","si37926","Button_70","si37958","si37971","Text_Caption_106","SmartShape_47","SmartShape_48"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":741},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide38015"}}},{"id":"Image_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_58","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_60","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_11","title":"Carbohydrate: Gatorade Bottle ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"1. Total Carbohydrate:  How many grams of carbohydrate? Is this source low, medium, or high in carbohydrate? 2. Dietary Fiber: Is this source low, medium, or high in dietary fiber? 3. Added Sugar: Is it less than 50 grams? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_15","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17555","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17568","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_16","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17600","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17613","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_41","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_42","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"50 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_108","title":"At 48 grams, it is less than 50 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_49","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_50","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_51","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17643","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_58","Image_60","Text_Caption_31","Button_15","si17555","si17568","Button_16","si17600","si17613","SmartShape_41","SmartShape_42","Text_Caption_107","Text_Caption_108","SmartShape_49","SmartShape_50","SmartShape_51"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1140},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17643"}}},{"id":"Image_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_62","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_61","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_20","title":"Carbohydrate: Knowledge Check ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"1. Total Carbohydrate:  How many grams of carbohydrate? Is this source low, medium, or high in carbohydrates? 2. Dietary Fiber: Is this source low, medium, or high in dietary fibers? 3. Added Sugar: Is the added sugar less than 50 grams? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_33","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19081","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19094","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_34","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19126","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19139","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide19159","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_62","Image_61","Text_Caption_43","Button_33","si19081","si19094","Button_34","si19126","si19139"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":588},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19159"}}},{"id":"Image_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_65","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38297q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38327","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"How many grams of carbohydrates are there? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"25 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38349_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"25 grams\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38360","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38364","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"29 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"29 grams\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39378","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39382","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"0 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39378_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"0 grams\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39393","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39397","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"120 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39393_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"120 grams\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39408","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39412","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"11 grams ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39408_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"11 grams\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38381","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38297q16","for":"Slide38297q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38398","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38297q16","for":"Slide38297q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38411","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38297q16","for":"Slide38297q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38368","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38297q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again - Look for the number next to “Total Carbohydrate” ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38297q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide38297","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_65","si38327","si38334","si38353","si38364","si39382","si39397","si39412","si38381","si38398","si38411","si38368","si51932"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide38297"},"question":{"interactionId":"38314","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"How many grams of carbohydrates are there?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"Image_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_66","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38998q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38854","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_149","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38866","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_150","title":"Is this source low, medium, or high in total carbohydrates? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38877","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_151","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38881","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_152","title":"Low in total carbohydrates. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38877_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low in total carbohydrates.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38888","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_153","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38892","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_154","title":"Medium in total carbohydrates. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38888_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium in total carbohydrates.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39438","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39442","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"High in total carbohydrates. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39438_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High in total carbohydrates.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38960","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_46","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38998q17","for":"Slide38998q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38998q17","for":"Slide38998q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38998q17","for":"Slide38998q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38930","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38998q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51945","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again - Remember the 5 and 20 rule. 0-5% Low; 5.1-19.9% Medium,  20%+ High. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38998q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide38998","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_66","si38854","si38866","si38881","si38892","si39442","si38960","si38972","si38984","si38930","si51945"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":123},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide38998"},"question":{"interactionId":"38827","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Is this source low, medium, or high in total carbohydrates?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"Image_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_67","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39184q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39040","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_155","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_156","title":"Is this source low, medium, or high in dietary fibers? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_157","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_158","title":"Low in dietary fibers. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"28","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low in dietary fibers.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39074","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_159","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39078","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_160","title":"Medium in dietary fibers. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39074_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"30","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium in dietary fibers.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39423","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39427","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"High in dietary fibers. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39423_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High in dietary fibers.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39146","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_47","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39184q18","for":"Slide39184q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39158","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39184q18","for":"Slide39184q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39170","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39184q18","for":"Slide39184q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39116","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39184q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51958","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again- Remember the 5 and 20 rule. 0-5% Low; 5.1-19.9% Medium,  20%+ High. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39184q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide39184","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_67","si39040","si39052","si39067","si39078","si39427","si39146","si39158","si39170","si39116","si51958"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":126},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide39184"},"question":{"interactionId":"39013","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Is this source low, medium, or high in dietary fibers?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Image_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_68","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39370q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39226","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_161","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_162","title":"Is the added sugar less than 50 grams? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39249","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_163","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39253","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_164","title":"Yes, the added sugar is less than 50 grams. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39249_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"32","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, the added sugar is less than 50 grams.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39260","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_165","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39264","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_166","title":"No, the added sugar is 50 grams or more.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39260_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"34","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, the added sugar is 50 grams or more. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39332","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_48","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39370q19","for":"Slide39370q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39344","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39370q19","for":"Slide39370q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39356","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39370q19","for":"Slide39370q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39302","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39370q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51608","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again - Check the value in the phrase “Includes __g Added Sugars”  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39370q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide39370","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_68","si39226","si39238","si39253","si39264","si39332","si39344","si39356","si39302","si51608"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide39370"},"question":{"interactionId":"39199","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Is the added sugar less than 50 grams?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Image_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_64","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_63","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_38","title":"Sour Patch Kids Summarization (Carbs Section) ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_88","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_88","title":"There are 29 grams of total carbohydrate. This food is a medium source of total carbohydrate, as it provides 11% of daily value This food is a low source of dietary fiber, as it provides 0%(or insignificant) There are 25 grams of sugar added and it provides 50% of daily value. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_71","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si38194","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si38207","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_72","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_72","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si38239","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si38252","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_52","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide38296","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_64","Image_63","Text_Caption_88","Button_71","si38194","si38207","Button_72","si38239","si38252","SmartShape_52"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":876},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide38296"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_33","title":"Cholesterol and Sodium ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_70","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","title":"Check the following %DV to see if it is low, medium, or high source 1. Sodium: Packaged and processed food products contain large amounts of sodium as a preservative and to give it flavor. Can increase blood pressure if it is not limited (no more than 2,300) 2. Cholesterol: Listed but it is based on an individual’s health goal and nutritional needs ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_61","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33911","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33924","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_62","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33956","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33969","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_69","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_109","title":"Low source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_110","title":"Medium source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_64","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_65","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33989","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_70","Text_Caption_62","Button_61","si33911","si33924","Button_62","si33956","si33969","Image_69","Text_Caption_109","Text_Caption_110","SmartShape_64","SmartShape_65"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1143},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33989"}}},{"id":"Image_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_81","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_82","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_22","title":"Cholesterol and Sodium: Cup of Noodles ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","title":"1. Sodium: Is this source low, medium, or high in sodium? 2. Cholesterol: Is this source low, medium, or high in cholesterol? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_35","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19335","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19348","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_36","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19380","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19393","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide19413","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_81","Image_82","Text_Caption_48","Button_35","si19335","si19348","Button_36","si19380","si19393"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":336},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19413"}}},{"id":"Image_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_83","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39826q20"},"question":{"quizId":389,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39863","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Is this source low, medium, or high in cholesterol? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39878","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39882","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Low source of cholesterol. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39878_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low source of cholesterol.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39889","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39893","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Medium source of cholesterol. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39889_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium source of cholesterol.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40085","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40089","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"High source of cholesterol. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40085_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High source of cholesterol.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39910","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39826q20","for":"Slide39826q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39927","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39826q20","for":"Slide39826q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39940","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39826q20","for":"Slide39826q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39897","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39826q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51971","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again- Remember the 5 and 20 rule. 0-5% Low; 5.1-19.9% Medium,  20%+ High. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39826q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide39826","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_83","si39856","si39863","si39882","si39893","si40089","si39910","si39927","si39940","si39897","si51971"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":102},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide39826"},"question":{"interactionId":"39843","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Is this source low, medium, or high in cholesterol?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"Image_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_84","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40281q21"},"question":{"quizId":389,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_167","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_168","title":"Is this source low, medium, or high in sodium? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40149","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_169","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40153","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_170","title":"Low source of sodium. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40149_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"36","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low source of sodium.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40160","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_171","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40164","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_172","title":"Medium source of sodium. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40160_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"38","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium source of sodium.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40171","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_173","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_174","title":"High source of sodium. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40171_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"40","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High source of sodium.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_51","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide40281q21","for":"Slide40281q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40255","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide40281q21","for":"Slide40281q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40267","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide40281q21","for":"Slide40281q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40281q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again- Remember the 5 and 20 rule. 0-5% Low; 5.1-19.9% Medium,  20%+ High. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40281q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide40281","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_84","si40126","si40138","si40153","si40164","si40175","si40243","si40255","si40267","si40213","si51984"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide40281"},"question":{"interactionId":"40111","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Is this source low, medium, or high in sodium?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"]}}},{"id":"Image_86","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_86","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_85","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_85","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_40","title":"Cholesterol and Sodium: Review ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_90","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_90","title":"This food is a low source of cholesterol, as it provides 0% of daily value. This food is a high source of sodium, as it provides 51% of daily value. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_76","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si40380","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si40393","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_77","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_77","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si40425","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si40438","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_62","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_63","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide40458","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_86","Image_85","Text_Caption_90","Button_76","si40380","si40393","Button_77","si40425","si40438","SmartShape_62","SmartShape_63"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":714},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide40458"}}},{"id":"Image_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_71","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_34","title":"Vitamins and Minerals ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":"Listed right below protein with their percent daily value (%DV) vitamin D (in micrograms)  calcium (in milligrams),  iron (in milligrams), potassium (in milligrams) Manufacturers can choose to label any additional vitamins and minerals It is only required if the vitamin or mineral was specifically added to the food product ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_63","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si34090","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si34103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_64","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si34135","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si34148","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_72","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_72","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_111","title":"Low source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_112","title":"Medium source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_113","title":"Low source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_114","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_114","title":"Medium source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_60","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34168","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_71","Text_Caption_63","Button_63","si34090","si34103","Button_64","si34135","si34148","Image_72","Text_Caption_111","Text_Caption_112","Text_Caption_113","Text_Caption_114","SmartShape_60"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":774},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34168"}}},{"id":"Image_74","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_74","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_39","title":"Vitamins and Minerals: Knowledge Check ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_89","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_89","title":"Four mentioned items Is this source low, medium, or high in vitamin D? Is this source low, medium, or high in calcium?  Is this source low, medium, or high in iron? Is this source low, medium, or high in potassium? Additional vitamins or minerals Are there other medium to high sources of vitamin and minerals present? If so, which ones. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_74","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_74","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si39717","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si39730","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_75","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si39762","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si39775","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_73","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_73","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide39795","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_74","Text_Caption_89","Button_74","si39717","si39730","Button_75","si39762","si39775","Image_73"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":639},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide39795"}}},{"id":"Image_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_75","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"question":{"quizId":389,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40639","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"This food item is a medium source of which of the following? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40661","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40665","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vitamin D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40665","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si40661_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vitamin D\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40672","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40676","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Calcium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40676","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si40672_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Calcium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40753","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40757","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Iron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40757","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si40753_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Iron\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40768","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40772","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Potassium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40772","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si40768_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Potassium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40787","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vitamin E ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40787","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si40783_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vitamin E\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40798","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40802","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Phosphorus ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40802","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si40798_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Phosphorus\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40813","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40817","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Magnesium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40817","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si40813_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Magnesium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si40693","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide40609q22","for":"Slide40609q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40710","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide40609q22","for":"Slide40609q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide40609q22","for":"Slide40609q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40680","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51997","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again- Remember the 5 and 20 rule. 0-5% Low; 5.1-19.9% Medium,  20%+ High. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide40609q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide40609","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_75","si40639","si40646","si40665","si40676","si40757","si40772","si40787","si40802","si40817","si40693","si40710","si40723","si40680","si51997"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":102},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide40609"},"question":{"interactionId":"40626","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"This food item is a medium source of which of the following?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C","D","E","F","G"]}}},{"id":"Image_77","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_77","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_76","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_41","title":"Clif Bar Summarization (Vitamins and Minerals) ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_91","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_91","title":"This food is a low source of  Vitamin D, as it provides 0% of daily value. Calcium, as it provides 4% of daily value. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_78","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si40952","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si40965","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_79","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si40997","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si41010","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_97","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_97","title":"This food is a medium source of:  Iron, as it provides 10% of daily value. Potassium, as it provides 6%of daily value. Vitamin E, as it provides 6% of daily value. Phosphorus, as it provides 15% of daily value. Magnesium, as it provides 15% of daily value. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_54","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_53","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_53","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_59","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_55","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_56","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_57","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_57","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_58","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide41041","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_77","Image_76","Text_Caption_91","Button_78","si40952","si40965","Button_79","si40997","si41010","Text_Caption_97","SmartShape_54","SmartShape_53","SmartShape_59","SmartShape_55","SmartShape_56","SmartShape_57","SmartShape_58"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":858},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide41041"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_25","title":"Interactive Edpuzzle: Using the Calorie and Macronutrient Journal Entry ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"Use the following Macronutrient and Calorie Journal (Google Sheet)  to work through this Edpuzzle.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_41","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19907","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19920","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19952","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19965","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Web_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Web_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19985","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_54","Button_41","si19907","si19920","Button_42","si19952","si19965","Web_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":294},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19985"}}},{"id":"si47373","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47289","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"1. What are some of the reasons why one should consider reading a nutrition label? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47311","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47315","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Help you track your nutritional intake. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47315","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47259q23"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si47311_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Help you track your nutritional intake.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si47322","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Provides information for a serving. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47326","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47259q23"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si47322_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Provides information for a serving.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si48304","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Improve your wrestling stamina. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48308","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47259q23"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si48304_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Improve your wrestling stamina.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si48319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Include tips on avoiding unhealthy food. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48323","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47259q23"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si48319_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Include tips on avoiding unhealthy food.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si48334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Offers personalized meal plans ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48338","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47259q23"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si48334_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Offers personalized meal plans\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si47369","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47259q23","for":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47394","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47259q23","for":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47407","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47259q23","for":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47419","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47259q23","for":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47436","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47259q23","for":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47449","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47259q23","for":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47461","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47259q23","for":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47478","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47259q23","for":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47491","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47259q23","for":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47356","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47259q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide47259","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si47289","si47296","si47315","si47326","si48308","si48323","si48338","si47377","si47394","si47407","si47419","si47436","si47449","si47461","si47478","si47491","si47356"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":111},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide47259"},"question":{"interactionId":"47276","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1. What are some of the reasons why one should consider reading a nutrition label?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A","B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si48575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_222","roles":{}},{"id":"si48392","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_219","roles":{}},{"id":"si48404","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_220","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48416","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_221","title":"2. What is the “5 and 20” Rule? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48427","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_257","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48431","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_258","title":"A rule that recommends 20 servings of fruits and vegetables to consume 5 days a week. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48427_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A rule that recommends 20 servings of fruits and vegetables to consume 5 days a week.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si48438","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_259","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48442","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_260","title":"A guideline that considers 5% or less of a nutrient to be low and 20% or more to be high ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48438_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A guideline that considers 5% or less of a nutrient to be low and 20% or more to be high\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si48449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_261","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48453","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_262","title":"A rule that suggests to drink 5 glasses of water a day and limiting to 20 ounces of soda a week ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48449_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A rule that suggests to drink 5 glasses of water a day and limiting to 20 ounces of soda a week\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si48460","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_263","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48464","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_264","title":"A standard procedure of warming up for 5 minutes, and following it with resistance training for 20 minutes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48460_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A standard procedure of warming up for 5 minutes, and following it with resistance training for 20 minutes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si48605","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide48727q24","for":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48617","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide48727q24","for":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48629","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide48727q24","for":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48647","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_3","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide48727q24","for":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48659","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide48727q24","for":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48671","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide48727q24","for":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48689","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_86","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide48727q24","for":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48701","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide48727q24","for":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48713","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide48727q24","for":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48569","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_73","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide48727q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide48727","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si48404","si48416","si48431","si48442","si48453","si48464","si48605","si48617","si48629","si48647","si48659","si48671","si48689","si48701","si48713","si48569"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide48727"},"question":{"interactionId":"48383","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. What is the “5 and 20” Rule?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_104","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48163","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si48021","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Matching ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48028","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48035","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48059","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48063","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48080","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48084","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Saturated Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48046","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48069","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48073","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Low Source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48073ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low Source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si48090","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48094","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Medium Source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48094ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium Source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si48111","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48115","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"High Source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48115ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High Source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si48159","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si48167","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47974q25","for":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47974q25","for":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48197","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47974q25","for":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48209","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47974q25","for":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48226","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47974q25","for":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48239","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47974q25","for":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48251","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47974q25","for":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48268","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47974q25","for":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48281","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47974q25","for":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51424","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47974q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide47974","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_104","si48021","si48028","si48073","si48094","si48115","si48167","si48184","si48197","si48209","si48226","si48239","si48251","si48268","si48281","si51424"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":177},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide47974"},"question":{"interactionId":"47991","quizId":389,"title":"Matching","text":"3. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients:\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_102","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47617","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47540","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"4. Based on trans fat, this food should be avoided. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47555","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47559","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True; This food should be avoided based on trans fat. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47555_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True; This food should be avoided based on trans fat.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si47566","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47570","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False; This food does not need to be avoided based on trans fat. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47566_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False; This food does not need to be avoided based on trans fat.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si47613","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47503q26","for":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47638","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47503q26","for":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47651","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47503q26","for":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47663","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47503q26","for":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47680","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47503q26","for":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47693","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47503q26","for":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47705","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47503q26","for":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47722","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47503q26","for":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47735","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47503q26","for":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47600","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47503q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide47503","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_102","si47533","si47540","si47559","si47570","si47621","si47638","si47651","si47663","si47680","si47693","si47705","si47722","si47735","si47600"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":108},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide47503"},"question":{"interactionId":"47520","quizId":389,"title":"True/False","text":"4. Based on trans fat, this food should be avoided.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_103","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48977","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_278","roles":{}},{"id":"si48777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_223","roles":{}},{"id":"si48789","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_224","title":"Matching ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48801","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_225","title":"5. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_226","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_267","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_267","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_268","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_268","title":"Total Carbohydrate ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_269","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_269","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_270","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_270","title":"Dietary Fiber ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49140","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49144","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Added Sugar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48845","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_271","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48849","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_272","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48853","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_273","title":"Low Source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48853ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low Source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si48859","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_274","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48863","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_275","title":"Medium Source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48863ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium Source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si48869","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_276","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48873","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_277","title":"High Source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48873ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High Source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si49007","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide49129q27","for":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49019","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide49129q27","for":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49031","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide49129q27","for":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide49129q27","for":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49061","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide49129q27","for":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49073","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide49129q27","for":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49091","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_87","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide49129q27","for":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49103","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide49129q27","for":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49115","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide49129q27","for":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si48971","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_74","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49129q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide49129","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_103","si48789","si48801","si48853","si48863","si48873","si49007","si49019","si49031","si49049","si49061","si49073","si49091","si49103","si49115","si48971"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":177},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide49129"},"question":{"interactionId":"48753","quizId":389,"title":"Matching","text":"5. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients:\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":[],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_106","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49399","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_296","roles":{}},{"id":"si49189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_279","roles":{}},{"id":"si49201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_280","title":"Matching ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_281","title":"6. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_282","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_283","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_284","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_284","title":"Vitamin D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_285","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_285","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_286","title":"Calcium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_287","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_287","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_288","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_288","title":"Iron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49563","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49567","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Potassium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49267","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_289","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49271","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_290","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49275","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_291","title":"Low Source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49275ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Low Source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si49281","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_292","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49285","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_293","title":"Medium Source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49285ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Medium Source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si49291","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_294","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49295","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_295","title":"High Source ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49295ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"High Source","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si49429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_20","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide49552q28","for":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49441","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide49552q28","for":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49453","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide49552q28","for":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49471","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_31","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide49552q28","for":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49483","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide49552q28","for":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49495","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide49552q28","for":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49513","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_88","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide49552q28","for":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49525","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide49552q28","for":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49537","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide49552q28","for":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51561","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49552q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide49552","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_106","si49201","si49213","si49275","si49285","si49295","si49429","si49441","si49453","si49471","si49483","si49495","si49513","si49525","si49537","si51561"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":177},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide49552"},"question":{"interactionId":"49158","quizId":389,"title":"Matching","text":"6. Use the provided nutrition label to describe the percent daily value per container of the following nutrients:\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":[],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_107","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49775","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_308","roles":{}},{"id":"si49603","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_297","roles":{}},{"id":"si49615","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_299","title":"7. Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per serving, which of the following would be considered medium in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_300","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_301","title":"Total Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49642","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si49638_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si49649","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_302","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49653","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_303","title":"Saturated Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49653","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si49649_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saturated Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si49660","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_304","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49664","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_305","title":"Cholesterol ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49664","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si49660_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cholesterol\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si49671","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_306","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49675","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_307","title":"Sodium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49675","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si49671_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sodium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si49948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49952","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Carbs ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49952","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si49948_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Carbs\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si49963","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49967","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Dietary Fibers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49967","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si49963_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Dietary Fibers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si49978","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Added Sugars ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49982","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si49978_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Added Sugars\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si49993","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"H) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49997","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vitamin D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49997","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si49993_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vitamin D\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50008","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50012","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Calcium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50012","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50008_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Calcium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50023","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"J) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50027","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Iron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50027","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50023_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Iron\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si53120","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"K) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si53124","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Potassium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si53124","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si53120_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Potassium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si49805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_32","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide49927q29","for":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49817","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide49927q29","for":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49829","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide49927q29","for":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49847","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_39","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide49927q29","for":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49859","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide49927q29","for":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49871","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide49927q29","for":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49889","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_89","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide49927q29","for":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49901","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide49927q29","for":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49913","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide49927q29","for":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si49769","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_80","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide49927q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide49927","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_107","si49615","si49627","si49642","si49653","si49664","si49675","si49952","si49967","si49982","si49997","si50012","si50027","si53124","si49805","si49817","si49829","si49847","si49859","si49871","si49889","si49901","si49913","si49769"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":222},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide49927"},"question":{"interactionId":"49594","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7. Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per serving, which of the following would be considered medium in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A","B","E","F","G","I"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_108","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50324","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","roles":{}},{"id":"si50086","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_309","roles":{}},{"id":"si50098","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_310","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_311","title":"8. Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per cookie, which of the following would be considered high in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_312","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50125","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_313","title":"Total Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50125","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"139","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50121_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"140","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_314","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50136","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_315","title":"Saturated Fat ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50136","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"141","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50132_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"142","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saturated Fat\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si50143","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_316","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_317","title":"Cholesterol ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"143","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50143_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"144","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cholesterol\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50154","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_318","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50158","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_319","title":"Sodium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50158","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"145","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50154_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"146","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sodium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50165","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_320","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_321","title":"Total Carbs ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"147","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50165_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"148","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Total Carbs\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50176","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_322","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_323","title":"Dietary Fibers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"149","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50176_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"150","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Dietary Fibers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_324","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_325","title":"Added Sugars ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"151","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50187_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"152","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Added Sugars\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_326","title":"H) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50202","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"Vitamin D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50202","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"153","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50198_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"154","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vitamin D\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50209","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"I) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Calcium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"155","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50209_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"156","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Calcium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_330","title":"J) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Iron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"157","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si50220_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"158","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Iron\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si53147","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"K) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si53151","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Potassium ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si53151","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si53147_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Potassium\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si50354","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_40","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide50476q30","for":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50366","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide50476q30","for":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50378","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide50476q30","for":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50396","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide50476q30","for":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50408","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide50476q30","for":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50420","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide50476q30","for":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50438","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_90","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide50476q30","for":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50450","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide50476q30","for":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50462","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide50476q30","for":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si50318","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_83","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide50476q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide50476","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_108","si50098","si50110","si50125","si50136","si50147","si50158","si50169","si50180","si50191","si50202","si50213","si50224","si53151","si50354","si50366","si50378","si50396","si50408","si50420","si50438","si50450","si50462","si50318"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":195},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide50476"},"question":{"interactionId":"50077","quizId":389,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. Based on the percent daily value (%DV) per cookie, which of the following would be considered high in that specific nutrient? Select all that apply\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A","B","E","F","G","J"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_109","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47835","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47769","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Fill-In-The-Blank ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47776","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"9. Complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47788","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"There are dash of total fat, dash of total carbohydrates, and dash of protein in this label. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47788_q1_answer_0_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47788_q1_answer_1_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47788_q1_answer_2_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47831","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si47839","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47747q31","for":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47747q31","for":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47869","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide47747q31","for":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47881","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47747q31","for":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47898","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47747q31","for":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47911","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide47747q31","for":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47923","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47747q31","for":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47940","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47747q31","for":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si47953","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide47747q31","for":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51548","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide47747q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide47747","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_109","si47769","si47776","si47839","si47856","si47869","si47881","si47898","si47911","si47923","si47940","si47953","si51548"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide47747"},"question":{"interactionId":"47763","quizId":389,"title":"Fill-In-The-Blank","text":"9. Complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"fill-in","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_391","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_391","title":"Link to the Macronutrient and Calorie Journal (Google Sheet). ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_392","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_392","title":"Link to the Nutrition Labels (Google Sheets) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51142","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_361","roles":{}},{"id":"si51010","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_357","roles":{}},{"id":"si51022","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_358","title":"Fill-In-The-Blank ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_359","title":"10. Use the labels(4) and the Macronutrient and Calorie Journal to complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51044","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_360","title":"For all four labels: “Total Calories is at dash “Total Fat” is at dash,  “Total Carbohydrates” is at dash,  and “Protein” is at  dash. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51044_q1_answer_0_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si51044_q1_answer_1_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si51044_q1_answer_2_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si51044_q1_answer_3_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si51172","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_59","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide51294q32","for":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide51294q32","for":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51196","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide51294q32","for":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51214","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_92","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide51294q32","for":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51226","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide51294q32","for":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51238","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide51294q32","for":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51256","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_93","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide51294q32","for":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51268","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide51294q32","for":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51280","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide51294q32","for":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51136","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_89","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide51294q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide51294","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_391","Text_Caption_392","si51022","si51034","si51172","si51184","si51196","si51214","si51226","si51238","si51256","si51268","si51280","si51136"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":186},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide51294"},"question":{"interactionId":"50982","quizId":389,"title":"Fill-In-The-Blank","text":"10. Use the labels(4) and the Macronutrient and Calorie Journal to complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks. \r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"fill-in","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si44233","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si44241","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si44249","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si44257","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si44265","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si44222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44229","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Maximum Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44245","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44253","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44261","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44277","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si44281","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44298","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44311","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44340","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si44353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide44208","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide44208"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_31","title":"Congratulations! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_53","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_53","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33062","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_54","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33094","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33107","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33120","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"Way to go! You have reached the end of this course!  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_18","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33161","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Button_53","si33062","Button_54","si33094","si33107","si33120","Text_Caption_60","Image_18"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":537},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33161"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_32","title":"References ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_55","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33245","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_56","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33277","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33290","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si33303","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"Mayo Clinic (2018). Heart-healthy diet: 8 steps to prevent heart disease. Retrieved from https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/heart-disease/in-depth/heart-healthy-diet/art-20047702 Images: Images are from Adobe Photo Stock.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33331","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Button_55","si33245","Button_56","si33277","si33290","si33303","Text_Caption_61"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":324},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33331"}}},{"id":"Pool433","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":433,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Module2WithPreTest","class":"project","title":"Module2WithPreTest","children":["Slide12004","Slide41512","Slide44078","Slide45048","Slide45064","Slide45527","Slide45508","Slide45914","Slide46433","Slide52703","Slide46809","Slide47118","Slide16578","Slide16781","Slide36193","Slide16973","Slide19595","Slide36194","Slide37504","Slide17427","Slide18241","Slide18378","Slide18515","Slide34271","Slide35151","Slide35337","Slide37779","Slide34946","Slide18706","Slide18843","Slide17859","Slide38015","Slide17643","Slide19159","Slide38297","Slide38998","Slide39184","Slide39370","Slide38296","Slide33989","Slide19413","Slide39826","Slide40281","Slide40458","Slide34168","Slide39795","Slide40609","Slide41041","Slide19985","Slide47259","Slide48727","Slide47974","Slide47503","Slide49129","Slide49552","Slide49927","Slide50476","Slide47747","Slide51294","Slide44208","Slide33161","Slide33331"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":389,"branched":true,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide44078q0","Slide45048q1","Slide45064q2","Slide45527q3","Slide45508q4","Slide45914q5","Slide46433q6","Slide52703q7","Slide46809q8","Slide47118q9","Slide36194q10","Slide37504q11","Slide34271q12","Slide35151q13","Slide35337q14","Slide37779q15","Slide38297q16","Slide38998q17","Slide39184q18","Slide39370q19","Slide39826q20","Slide40281q21","Slide40609q22","Slide47259q23","Slide48727q24","Slide47974q25","Slide47503q26","Slide49129q27","Slide49552q28","Slide49927q29","Slide50476q30","Slide47747q31","Slide51294q32"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":180,"passScore":144}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":true},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":true,"playPause":false,"back":false,"forward":false,"rewind":false,"close":false,"mute":true,"progressBar":false}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide12004","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide41512","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide44078","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide45048","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide45064","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide45527","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide45508","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide45914","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide46433","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide52703","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide46809","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide47118","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide16578","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide16781","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide36193","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide16973","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide19595","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide36194","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide37504","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide17427","title":"branching"},{"id":"Slide18241","title":"Slide 21"},{"id":"Slide18378","title":"Slide 22"},{"id":"Slide18515","title":"Slide 23"},{"id":"Slide34271","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide35151","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide35337","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide37779","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide34946","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide18706","title":"Slide 29"},{"id":"Slide18843","title":"Slide 30"},{"id":"Slide17859","title":"Slide 31"},{"id":"Slide38015","title":"Slide 32"},{"id":"Slide17643","title":"Slide 33"},{"id":"Slide19159","title":"Slide 34"},{"id":"Slide38297","title":"Slide 35"},{"id":"Slide38998","title":"Slide 36"},{"id":"Slide39184","title":"Slide 37"},{"id":"Slide39370","title":"Slide 38"},{"id":"Slide38296","title":"Slide 39"},{"id":"Slide33989","title":"Slide 40"},{"id":"Slide19413","title":"Slide 41"},{"id":"Slide39826","title":"Slide 42"},{"id":"Slide40281","title":"Slide 43"},{"id":"Slide40458","title":"Slide 44"},{"id":"Slide34168","title":"Slide 45"},{"id":"Slide39795","title":"Slide 46"},{"id":"Slide40609","title":"Slide 47"},{"id":"Slide41041","title":"Slide 48"},{"id":"Slide19985","title":"Slide 49"},{"id":"Slide47259","title":"Slide 50"},{"id":"Slide48727","title":"Slide 51"},{"id":"Slide47974","title":"Slide 52"},{"id":"Slide47503","title":"Slide 53"},{"id":"Slide49129","title":"Slide 54"},{"id":"Slide49552","title":"Slide 55"},{"id":"Slide49927","title":"Slide 56"},{"id":"Slide50476","title":"Slide 57"},{"id":"Slide47747","title":"Slide 58"},{"id":"Slide51294","title":"Slide 59"},{"id":"Slide44208","title":"Slide 60"},{"id":"Slide33161","title":"Slide 61"},{"id":"Slide33331","title":"Slide 62"}]}